Contact

chandan.urdream@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/meetchandan (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Java MySQL J2EE Web Services

Languages

Hindi (Full Professional)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

AMCAT Certified Software Engineer - IT Services

Chandan Kumar

Java Developer ★Full stack developer ★Microservice and cloud native app developer

Bengaluru

Summary

Having total 6 years and 4 months of experience in Software Engineering, working as a Java, Full stack and Cloud developer.

T-shaped developer where app development is core competency while collaboration with Business Analyst and quality analyst are other qualities.

Currently working for SAP Labs as full stack developer for cloud native app.

Earlier worked for CGI and Jpmorgan chase for 37 months and 27 months respectively as a Java developer.

Extensive knowledge in developing Microservices and cloud native applications using Spring Boot, core Java, datastructure, J2EE, Spring, Hibernate, Spring Data Jpa, SQL, MySql, Angular 6, HTML 5.

An effective communicator with excellent relationship management skills and strong analytical, challenge oriented, problem solving & organizational abilities.

Experience

SAP Labs India Developer June 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Banglore

JPMorgan Chase & Co. Associate February 2017 - May 2019 (2 years 4 months)

Page 1 of 2

Hyderabad Area, India

CGI

Associate Software Engineer
December 2013 - February 2017 (3 years 3 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Education

Acharya Institute Of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering (BEng), Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2009 - 2013)

Kendriya vidyalaya

12th, physics, chemistry, Maths · (2006 - 2008)

pratibha pallavan public school

Matriculation, science · (1995 - 2006)